# Trey Alexander

Location: Springfield, MO, 65804 Phone number: 417-761-2121 Email: treyaalex47@gmail.com

GitHub: https://github.com/ArcadeRaven

GitHub Portfolio: https://arcaderaven.github.io/TreyAlexanderPortfolio.github.io/

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/trey-alexander-034098243/

## My Personal Profile

Computer science graduate with a focus on Python and C++ development. I have worked in Agile and Waterfall methodologies across several teams to develop unique software. Unreal 5 engine experience on both frontend and backend. This includes knowledge on landscaping, lighting, materials, textures, and blueprints.

With my time in an IT department and coding in teams, I am excellent at documentation, working in a team, collaborating with other teams; and getting work done without supervision. I am also able to troubleshoot errors and bugs, as well as understand code written by others.

### Core Skills

Agile	Waterfall	Code Review
Collaboration	Documentation	GitHub
Python	C++	Unreal Engine 5

## Highlighted Electives

- CSC 525: Graphic Rendering using C++ OpenGL and GLUT
- CSC 540: Introduction to Artificial Intelligence

## Fluent Languages

- HTML and CSS
- Django
- Python
- C++
- PostgreSQL

### **Education**

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science – Missouri State University

Minor of Mathematics – Missouri State University AUGUST 2022

### **Projects**

**Sunset Tomb:** A solo art project in Unreal 5 utilizing meshes, textures, Blueprints, textures, lighting, and wind speed.

**Study Assist:** I created a website in a team-based, AGILE environment using HTML, CSS, and Django / Python for front-end and back-end integration. This project is in my portfolio.

**Pokémon-Showdown AI:** I created a smart AI with a partner in Python that used the Minmax algorithm to play Pokémon Showdown. We used Pandas and a Pokémon-Showdown API. This project is in my portfolio.

## Work Experience

#### September 2021 to Present – Toth and Associates

Title: IT Intern

- Working on user tickets to solve hardware and software related issues.
- Documenting solutions.
- Active Directory experience.
- Assisting remote users on calls.

#### November 2016 to September 2021 – Walgreens

Title: Pharmacy technician and "designated hitter"

- Inventory management.
- Balancing time across multiple departments and responsibilities.

# Organizations and Hobbies

Missouri State League of Legends – Spring 2018 to Spring 2022